[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はなし' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "呼びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みせます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "話します"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はじめます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "話し"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おしえます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "見せます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅう, しょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "始めます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふります' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "教えます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'なまえ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "住所"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すぐ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "降ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しお' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "名前"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さとう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "直ぐ"
    }
]
